<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food and Drink &#8211; Preview Personnel Microsoft</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/food-and-drink/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 20:54:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Food and Drink &#8211; Preview Personnel Microsoft</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia Opens Its First-ever Alcohol Store</title>
		<link>/saudi-arabia-opens-its-first-ever-alcohol-store/</link>
					<comments>/saudi-arabia-opens-its-first-ever-alcohol-store/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 18:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food and Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia Opens Its First-ever Alcohol Store]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has opened its first alcohol store in the diplomatic quarter of its capital Riyadh, two sources told . The news, which has not been officially confirmed by the Saudi government, marks a major breakthrough for the highly conservative...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Saudi Arabia has opened its first alcohol store in the diplomatic quarter of its capital Riyadh, two sources told . The news, which has not been officially confirmed by the Saudi government, marks a major breakthrough for the highly conservative Muslim theocracy where alcohol has been banned since 1952. According to a list of store rules seen by , the venue is only accessible to non-Muslim diplomats, and authorization must be validated through an app called Diplo. No guests or people under the age of 21 are allowed to accompany authorized visitors to the store, photography is strictly prohibited and mobile phones need to be kept in secure mobile pouches so as not to be used while in the store. Purchases are also subject to a monthly quota system per registered individual.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Rumors have abounded for years that the Gulf kingdom, known for its ultraconservative laws, would eventually allow alcohol outside of foreign embassies as part of its broader campaign to liberalize Saudi society and draw more international tourists and expats. A shop in the diplomatic quarter is a small step in that direction, one Saudi consultant close to the kingdom’s royal court told . It’s a baby step to opening up alcohol sales to non-Muslims in Saudi Arabia eventually, to hotels and other venues, said the consultant, who requested anonymity due to the sensitivity of the topic. They added that one key objective is to deal with the smuggling problem that we’ve always had with diplomats. Foreign embassy staff, who are able to import alcohol to be kept on embassy premises, are known in Saudi Arabia to often import booze in large quantities and then sell it on the black market.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">A Western diplomat based in Riyadh, who requested anonymity due to professional restrictions, said that their colleagues had already visited the store and that it is extremely well stocked. has contacted Saudi Arabia’s ministries of media and foreign affairs for comment. Saudi Arabia has undergone seismic change both socially and economically in the years since the young Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, now the kingdom’s de-facto ruler, came to power. His brainchild, Vision 2030, is a multitrillion-dollar campaign to remake the Gulf country’s image, attract tourism and diversify its economy away from oil. The kingdom has seen a series of liberalizing reforms implemented since Crown Prince Mohammed came to power, with Saudi Arabia allowing previously banned things like women driving, movie theaters and concerts, while simultaneously cracking down on dissent and imprisoning political activists.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/saudi-arabia-opens-its-first-ever-alcohol-store/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>MSG Is The Most Misunderstood Ingredient Of The Century</title>
		<link>/msg-is-the-most-misunderstood-ingredient-of-the-century/</link>
					<comments>/msg-is-the-most-misunderstood-ingredient-of-the-century/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 18:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food and Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MSG Is The Most Misunderstood Ingredient Of The Century]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=595</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Calvin Eng, the owner of New York-based Cantonese-American restaurant Bonnie’s, isn’t shy about his love for monosodium glutamate. Case in point – he has the letters MSG tattooed on his arm, and his restaurant’s menu includes a signature drink called...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Calvin Eng, the owner of New York-based Cantonese-American restaurant Bonnie’s, isn’t shy about his love for monosodium glutamate. Case in point – he has the letters MSG tattooed on his arm, and his restaurant’s menu includes a signature drink called the MSG Martini. Things just taste better with MSG, whether it’s Western food or Cantonese food, the chef tells CNN. We use it in drinks. We use it in desserts. We use it in savory food. It’s in almost everything. Salt, sugar and MSG – I always joke that they’re the Chinese Trinity of seasonings. Openly admitting to using MSG – once a surefire way to keep your restaurant empty – certainly hasn’t undermined Bonnie’s success. It’s become one of the hottest tables in New York since opening in Williamsburg, Brooklyn in late 2021, winning numerous Best New Restaurant awards from multiple media outlets. Eng himself was named one of the best new chefs of 2022 by Food and Wine Magazine and was included on the 2023 Forbes 30 under 30 list, just to name a few of his recent achievements.</p>
<h4 style="text-align: justify;">What is in MSG?</h4>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Many didn’t know that MSG is plant-derived, says Tia Rains, a Chicago-based nutrition scientist and Ajinomoto’s vice president of customer engagement and strategic development. Our process [of making MSG] is by fermentation, which is very similar to how beer is brewed or how yogurt is made. First, plants with sugar – like sugarcanes or corn – are fermented with microbes to create glutamate, an amino acid found in food that’s also produced in our body and acts as a neurotransmitter. Then, sodium is added and the glutamate is crystalized to become the salt-like MSG we see in supermarkets and kitchens now. I’m a scientist by training. I think how MSG works is one of the coolest scientific things, says Rains. We have different receptors on our tongue for different tastes. Our receptor for umami looks almost like a Venus Flytrap under a microscope, she adds, mimicking a C with her hand.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Sounds complicated? You’ve probably been playing with glutamate, inosinate and guanylate in your own cooking without even realizing it. Carrots and onions (high in glutamate), for example, boost the umami-ness in beef (high in inosinate). Bonito fish (inosinate) and seaweed kombu (glutamate) also combine to create a powerful umami flavor. Foods like tomatoes and cheese even have natural glutamate in them. When people tell me that they ate at a Chinese food restaurant and they had trouble breathing and tightness in their chest, I get worried – and I’d say, ‘you need to follow up on that because MSG is not an allergen. It’s not going to cause an allergic response. Our bodies make glutamate, so it would not be possible to have an allergy to glutamate’,” says Rains. Despite continued claims of negative reactions to MSG from diners, decades of scientific trials have failed to prove the existence of MSG sensitivity. Government organizations around the world have listed MSG as safe to eat. This includes the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA), which lists MSG as “generally recognized as safe” (GRAS).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/msg-is-the-most-misunderstood-ingredient-of-the-century/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emerging Brands Grab Market Share in China and South Korea</title>
		<link>/emerging-brands-grab-market-share-in-china-and-south-korea/</link>
					<comments>/emerging-brands-grab-market-share-in-china-and-south-korea/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food and Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Emerging Brands Grab Market Share in China and South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The rise of online shopping, social media and easier access to factories are driving the growth of new consumer brands in parts of Asia — putting pressure on traditional industry giants. Over the last several years, such upstart consumer brands...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The rise of online shopping, social media and easier access to factories are driving the growth of new consumer brands in parts of Asia — putting pressure on traditional industry giants. Over the last several years, such upstart consumer brands have been gaining market share in China and South Korea, according to a report from Bain and Company released Monday. The consumer products company of the future is going to need to be constantly reinventing its brand portfolio, said David Zehner, head of consumer practice at Bain.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">If you’re able to both leverage the advantages that your scale and your incumbent position creates, while also being nimble and agile and responsive to the consumer, he said, then there is a chance that you can win, even despite the difficult environment, because there are so many insurgents. Bain defines an insurgent brand as a business that generates more than $25 million in annual revenues, has grown more than 10 times in their category’s average growth rate over the last five years and is independent or has been bought by a large firm in the last 2 years.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Incumbents are leaders in the sector and have a firm position in the market. For example, sponge brand Scrub Daddy is an insurgent brand while its competitor Scotch-Brite is an incumbent one. The company studied 23 consumer product goods categories across 11 Asia-Pacific markets from 2018 to 2022 to find out whether insurgent and incumbent brands were thriving or struggling in the countries surveyed. China and South Korea stood out as markets where insurgent brands were doing particularly well. Incumbent brands only grabbed market share in eight out of 23 sectors in China — sports, bath and shower, skincare, confectionery, sweet biscuits, milk formula, drinking milk products and juice, the Bain report said. In South Korea, incumbent brands dominated just four sectors — fragrances, confectionery, diapers and bottled water, the report showed.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>E-commerce boost</strong><br />
China and South Korea’s thriving e-commerce scene has made it easier for insurgents to penetrate these highly competitive sectors, Zehner highlighted. Online shopping accounted for 34% of 2022 retail sales in South Korea, and 27% of such sales in China, the report said. We see a lot of brand launches in a market like China because it’s easy to reach consumers. It has become quite tough as an incumbent brand in those categories because you constantly have all of these new competitors, Zehner told CNBC. The country’s insurgent friendly market is also due to the boom in live streaming, he added, referring to a sales practice where sellers show and talk about products on social media to attract customers.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">High penetration of e-commerce in Indonesia (26%) and Singapore (13%) also gave insurgent brands a boost. Incumbent ones only grew market share in seven and three sectors, respectively, out of 23 categories in each country, the Bain report said. In contrast, emerging brands remain popular in Malaysia, the Philippines and India due to lower popularity of e-commerce and higher levels of traditional trade. All three developing countries saw e-commerce sales penetration of less than 8% in 2022.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Fast-moving consumer trends</strong><br />
New consumer preferences, often influenced by social media, are generating demand for brands that can adapt quickly. In South Korea, Zehner pointed out that new brands were able to benefit from trends in which people change their whole wardrobe every season because what is popular has moved so quickly. That’s in apparel. Same thing goes on in other consumer goods as well, he said. Industry structures are also fragmenting, allowing consumers and small business owners to communicate directly with factories. There’s also this ecosystem of third-party suppliers that allow a brand owner to very quickly outsource any part of its business if it needs to, Zehner said, noting that rather than having to invest heavily upfront, new companies can find partners for every step. By product, Bain found that insurgent hair care and skin care companies were the most popular among consumers, but when it came to confectionary, they preferred established brands.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">It’s also unclear how long new brands can survive in such a competitive environment. For any one of those insurgents you may become very popular very quickly because of the ability to reach consumers so easily, but then you become a casualty of the next trend, Zehner said.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Incumbent brands still hot</strong><br />
Bain’s findings revealed that despite the leaps insurgent brands have made in some markets, incumbent brands have maintained or increased their market share in others. There was no single sector in which incumbents lost share across all Asia-Pacific markets, nor a single market where they lost share in all categories, according to the report. For example, in the color cosmetics category, established brands won in two markets, lost in seven and remained stable in Singapore and Vietnam. There are trends, there are patterns but there are a lot of nuances and exceptions, Zehner said. If you are an incumbent [brand] and you miss a new consumer trend and someone else gets it and grows the brand very quickly, you then have a choice — you can try to defend your existing position, you can try to innovate and find the next consumer trend, or try to acquire the brand that has just grown, Zehner pointed out. He added that during the pandemic, customers temporarily returned to brands they knew and trusted, and which had a more secured supply chain in place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/emerging-brands-grab-market-share-in-china-and-south-korea/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World’s Best Soups</title>
		<link>/the-worlds-best-soups/</link>
					<comments>/the-worlds-best-soups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Food and Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The World’s Best Soups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If a steaming bowl of soup strikes you as the ultimate in old-fashioned comfort, you’ve got plenty of company. Soup is one of the world’s oldest and most universal foods, said Janet Clarkson, author of the book Soup: A Global...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">If a steaming bowl of soup strikes you as the ultimate in old-fashioned comfort, you’ve got plenty of company. Soup is one of the world’s oldest and most universal foods, said Janet Clarkson, author of the book Soup: A Global History. Every culture has some kind of soup, she said. It’s got very ancient roots. Early people simmered it in everything from turtle shells to lengths of bamboo, she writes in the book, turning out metal soup pots starting in the Bronze Age.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Boiling food made it possible to subsist on stable grains, with herbs and other ingredients added for nourishment or medicinal purposes. Each time you deliver a pot of hearty soup (with perhaps a side of bread) to a friend with the sniffles, Clarkson said you’re in fact carrying on an age-old tradition. Separating food and medicine — that’s not how ancient people thought of it, she said. I think in every country in the world, historically, some soups were seen as restorative.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">That’s true no matter what you call it. Today, soup leans brothy while stews are more substantial, but the world’s spoonable foods have never fit neatly into the two English-language categories. While Clarkson dove into centuries of etymology to trace the history of soup, potage and broth, she settled on a generously broad take. Just some stuff cooked in water, she wrote, with the flavored water becoming a crucial part of the dish. It’s a definition that leaves room for the world’s tremendous culinary diversity. These are CNN Travel’s nominations for 20 of the best soups around the world:</p>
<h4 style="text-align: justify;">Banga | Nigeria</h4>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Fruits from the oil palm tree lend both fat and flavor to this soup from the Niger Delta, which also features fresh catfish, beef and dried seafood. It’s so popular that packets of ready-mixed banga spice are sold in shops. Most blends include African nutmeg, castor seed, orima, jansa and beletete leaves. The spices infuse a rich, red sauce that’s the soup’s main draw: Soak it up with eba or a ball of starch, two Nigerian staples both made from cassava prepared with different methods.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-worlds-best-soups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
